http://www.unbelievabra.com/pages/privacy-policy

FOAM CUP STYLES Full-coverage and tank-style backs with underwire molded foam cups.
NON-FOAM STYLESFor larger cup sizes with a non-foam cup that won't add to your breast size.
WIRELESS STYLESWirefree Bralette and Long w/ Removable Foam Padding
Comfeez Wirefree Styles
SPORTS BRA Shape and support that minimizes bounce, without creating "uniboob".
PROTECTIVE MASKWashable 2-layer surgical style pleated ear-loop mask with embedded flexible nose piece wire.
Protective Face Mask
FOAM CUP STYLES Full-coverage and tank-style backs with underwire molded foam cups.
NON-FOAM STYLESFor larger cup sizes with a non-foam cup that won't add to your breast size.
WIRELESS STYLESWirefree Bralette and Long w/ Removable Foam Padding
Comfeez Wirefree Styles
SPORTS BRA Shape and support that minimizes bounce, without creating "uniboob".
PROTECTIVE MASKWashable 2-layer surgical style pleated ear-loop mask with embedded flexible nose piece wire.
Updated 11/12/14
Shapeez has created this privacy statement because we believe you have a right to a safe, secure online shopping experience. We are committed both to protecting your privacy and informing you how information from you will be used. If you still have concerns or questions after reading this policy, please contact us.
Q: When I visit Shapeez.com, what information is gathered about me and why?
Shapeez does collect certain customer information. We use this information to process orders, enhance your shopping experience and communicate with our customers.
We use order forms that allow you to buy our products. We collect your name, e-mail address, postal address, and credit card information. This information is used to process and send orders. We also use this information to contact you in case there is a question or problem with an order.
When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may collect your name, e-mail address, and other demographic information, such as zip code, age, or income level. We use this contact information to send you information about our company and to contact you if necessary.
We also use data collected when you register, enter a contest, and make purchases to enhance and personalize your shopping experience. We may also send you email about Shapeez updates and product offerings. You can unsubscribe to these emails at any time.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer this website. We log IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to track a user’s specific session, or to investigate cases of fraud or other security violations on our site. Any personally identifiable information contained in our IP address logs will be treated with the same respect for your privacy that order and registration information is treated.
Q: What are cookies and should I worry about them?
Cookies are small pieces of information that many web sites use to make online navigation easier. This data is contained on your hard drive in a file which your web browser provides for the purpose. A cookie can contain information such as a user ID. Our site can’t read other data on your hard drive or read cookies created by other sites.
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and, if you choose to register with us or request to receive email from Shapeez, to deliver content specific to your interests. You do not need to have cookies turned on to view our site, but you will need to accept cookies to register or order products.
Q: Who else has access to the information I provide to Shapeez?
Shapeez does not sell, rent, or give away your personal information to anyone. We do supplement financial information for the purpose of billing and shipping your order. In other words, we do get approval from the credit card company and do give the shipper your address. The other form of third party information that may be used is personally identifiable information submitted for another person by you. For instance, if you want to buy a gift for a friend and have it shipped to them; or, if you complete a “tell a friend” form on our site.
Q: What is Shapeez doing to protect my privacy?
This site has security measures in place to protect from the loss, misuse, and alteration of information under our control. Our servers use encrypted methods for those pages which contain personally identifiable data, including your credit card and address. We routinely check our security systems to ensure that we use the best security technology available.
We at Shapeez are sincerely committed to a safe and secure web experience for our visitors. If, after reading all this, you have concerns or questions, by all means, get in touch with us.
Security
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES–256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it. If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.
Questions & Contact Information
If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at dberner@shapeez.com Or by mail at:
Shapeez Re: Privacy Compliance Officer 200 Perry Parkway, Suite #10 Gaithersburg, Maryland 20877 USA
Subscribe Get exclusive notifications on sales and specials not listed on our website!Subscribe now and Get $10 Off your next order of $50 or more.(Some restrictions apply.)
COMFEEZ SHORT FIT GUIDESmall:34AA - DD 32DDD - EMedium:36AA - DD34DDD - ELarge:38/40AA - DD36DDD - EX-Large:42A - DD40DDD - E1X:44A - DD42DDD
Small: 34AA-DD        32DDD-EMedium: 36AA-DD34DDD-ELarge: 38/40AA-DD36DDD-EX-Large: 42A-DD40DDD-E1X: 44A-DD42DDD
COMFEEZ SHORT FIT GUIDESmall:34AA - DD 32DDD - EMedium:36AA - DD34DDD - ELarge:38/40AA - DD36DDD - EX-Large:42A - DD40DDD - E1X:44A - DD42DDD
